Once again, do it now.
Thank you.
Okay, alright.
Mode nash no survival day.
Get away from.
I don't wanna play.
Let's go, go.
Come and find a way.
Break out, we tell me no.
Break out.
Don't worry.
Ours.
Keep up.
But don't worry.
Unmey. You can turn.
I don't stop beating.
Don't stop beating.
I'm out.
All right, Sports Maximum.
Listen carefully.
On Earth, much akin to how the ratio of
water to land is seven parts to three,
the souls of living things
have a perfect set amount.
It's crucial to maintain
the balance of things.
As the population of Earth increases,
it wouldn't be a mistake to assume that
in accordance with that rising number,
the same amount of living
creatures are in decline.
It would appear that the number of souls
that exist in full is a fixed constant.
But let me posit a theory.
What if one person were able
to possess several more,
or perhaps even thousands
more souls simultaneously?
What do you think such a
person has the power to see?
What will that person's future hold?
And how soon will it come to pass?
Well, I have absolutely no idea,
but it's definitely a fascinating
concept to imagine coming true!
So then, what is it you
want me to do exactly?
Well, sports maximum!
My request to you has to do
with this specific bone I hold.
I want you to use your power to
attempt to modify the state of this.
Do you think you can take
this bone and resurrect it?
Whose is it?
Is it from a human body or something else?
That is irrelevant to you.
Let's just say I took possession
of it from an old friend.
But it's just one single piece
of a far more complex hole.
How can I resurrect that?
Or do you have a stockpile of all
his other assorted bones somewhere?
Is it possible to resurrect
something from just one bone?
Geo?
This is the one bone of his that remains.
The rest became dust and
scattered like ashes on the wind.
No longer of this world.
You must do this for me, sports maximum!
But if you're incapable of it,
well then I'll be forced to take back
in full the power I gave you before.
Believe me, I understand that.
But don't worry because
I've already done it.
That's right.
I've already finished.
You're welcome.
What the hell is this?
The boom!
Where did it go?
Start talking right now!
Where is it?
What did you do with the bone, fool?
I'm asking you!
Where his bone went?
You best answer me!
I swear, I don't know!
I mean, are we sure it's really Days?
I can't control it with my power.
I'm just not strong enough.
It's bizarre to imagine it would
move around on its own, but...
Yes, it's here somewhere. I can sense it.
I can actually feel it moving
within the walls of this room.
Find it!
Start looking right now!
No.
No, not yet.
Wait a minute, Sports Maximum.
This can only mean that
I was right all along.
That the way to heaven he kept
tantalizing me with does in fact exist,
and this proves it.
The search will continue,
but let's suspend it for now.
It's quite obvious.
We must let it decide its own course.
I'll observe it first,
then combine it with
Jotaro Kujo's memories for
everyone to find out the
real truth once and for all!
I can feel the bone's presence at the
Maximum Security disciplinary wing,
right as we speak.
It seems someone might
have picked it up, though.
What you saw were Sports Maximum's
memories that Aramis found by chance.
Of course, Jolene's seen this, too.
What?
Did Jolene make it so she can
go to the discipline cell?
just to find that same
bone belonging to Dio?
Yeah, but it's way too reckless.
Pale Snake is definitely going to do
his best to take out Jolene for good,
especially now that Sports
Maximum's memories were discovered.
If Jolene stays there by
herself, she's done for.
The only reason I'm alive
right now is Jolene, that's it.
But now, I have no idea
what I'm supposed to do.
Isn't there any way you can help me?
Oh, no. Oh,
even weather forecast who's
recovering in the medical
wing now wouldn't be able
to go over there either.
I really want to be helpful
in some way too, but
the isolated strict discipline
cell in the maximum security
disciplinary wing is on the
southeast side of the men's wing.
To get there,
you have to get on the prisoner transport
vehicle so there's no shortcut or bypass.
I've never even been there,
despite knowing that.
That's why I can't protect Jolene.
It's all I want to do,
but I don't know how.
I'm not asking you to protect her.
All I need from you is to take me
to that building on the down low.
Hey, Crisscross, are you
available to help us?
Forget Anastasia.
You can't rely on him.
Why not?
He's a stand user, isn't he?
Hey, were you born with
this power or what?
You see, it's like I told you.
Anastasia's not worth it.
That guy will never cooperate.
No matter what.
How come?
It's because...
I'll do anything if you'll help us!
If you get me to the
Discipline Cell building,
I swear I'll make it worth your while.
What do you say, buddy?
How about it?
Stop, FF!
Just let it go!
Both kindness and generosity just
aren't part of his personality. Huh?
I mean...
Um, wait, so you haven't
heard of the name Anastasia?
He's a cold-blooded murderer.
In fact, his full name
is Narciso Anastasia.
Don't know what might have triggered
it, but since he was a child,
he's had one bizarre habit.
No, it's not so much a
habit as it is a syndrome.
One that compels him to take
everything he touches apart.
There's seemingly no limit to
what he'll dismantle either.
When he was ten,
he took apart a neighbor's Porsche, and
he was in the hospital for six months.
He's even taken apart a
high-voltage telephone pole.
And one time, when he was 21,
he went to visit his then-girlfriend,
showing up unannounced late
that night at her apartment.
When he opened the door, he found
her in bed with another man.
He wanted to ensure they'd
never be together again,
so he separated them into dozens of
irreparable pieces.
He was arrested and went through
a psychiatric evaluation.
The results
were normal, and that's why he
ended up here at the aquarium.
There was no telling what he would
do if weather forecast wasn't
holding him down for safety's sake.
That's who he really is.
So Please forget it.
Shit, but I have to get to Jolene,
and I'll never make it by myself.
I need reinforcements.
I mean, if I could ask for a
perfect backup, it'd be him.
But it's bizarre, this feeling.
If asking nicely won't work, I'll
let my FF bullets do the talking.
They're pretty persuasive. Damn it!
As it stands, though, there's a pretty
good chance my first shot will go way wide.
Where am I even supposed to aim?
I have to go in like it's the kill shot.
Otherwise, he won't even
acknowledge me, much less obey me.
It's unnerving, but I have to do it.
That's the whole reason why I came here.
Okay, I'll help you.
If you really want, I'll
protect Jolene Kujo.
Huh?
I will, as you say, cooperate.
Also,
if she's looking for that bone or whatever
it is that seems to be in such demand,
Then I'll help find that, too.
We have to go.
She might be getting attacked
even as we speak right now.
Wait! Anastasia!
What are you scheming to do?
Me? Scheming?
No, it's just as I said.
I'll protect her with every
power I have. But... but you...
Honestly, I've come to like her.
Everything about her from my first view.
For example, I respect her resolve to go
to the discipline cell for her father.
She's quite admirable,
to say the very least.
If I keep her safe through this,
then I plan on making her my bride.
That's the condition.
Got it?
You're FF, right?
You said you'll do anything, didn't you?
All right then, give us your blessing.
No marriage is official without one.
Huh?
Did he just say what I think he said?
Am I going insane here?
He wants to marry Jolene?
Diver, drive!
What the hell was that?
Putzai, you set off a bomb
in there, you're dead!
So it's in the wall, with the time delay?
Yes, that's Anastasia's stand.
He has the power of diver drive.
Give us your blessings.
Find an occupation that
best fits their true
personality a king would
feel like a king and a chef
would feel like a chef
see that's what it means
to live truly the same goes
for stands strength and
weakness do not apply i
phrase that badly i meant
it more like when little
kids debate about who'd win
in a fight say stallone
or van Diam in that case
the stand i named survivor
Survivor is the weakest.
It's beyond control.
Survivor?
The name sounds strong, though.
It was the year 1982.
In the Lorraine region of France, a
group of six hikers met with disaster.
All six of them perished horribly.
After the recon team examined the
area where the tragedy occurred,
they found evidence of brutal combat.
They had all fought
literally to the death.
they had attacked one
another with so much force
their bones shattered
instantly upon contact
a tooth that had broken
off after being struck
was found half buried in
a nearby rock the damage
was so horrific even
the so-called winner was
hurt too badly to descend
and died of his wounds
as well as i found out
later those people had
stayed at a mountain hut
the night before and had an
altercation with the owner
of it one of the women
there crudely insulted
the man in fact she told
him his body odor was
vile is it safe to assume
the owner of the hut was
the stand user that's right
but what did the owner do
what was it that compelled
those people to fight
each other to the death
the answer is nothing at
all nothing externally
at least But deep in the
recesses of his brain,
anger was slowly beginning to brew.
Before much longer, that anger evolved
enough to become a weak electric signal.
This signal then descended
through his entire
nervous system and flowed into the ground.
That is Survivor.
The electric signal traveled
along the surface of the ground,
directly toward the six people.
For the ground and shoes to better conduct
electricity, the ground needs to be wet.
The electrical power a
nerve carries at any given
time measures a mere seven
hundredths of a volt.
That's how little power that stand has.
Survivor's attacks make one feel
nothing, and it does nothing.
Its effects don't come close to things like
severely injuring or controlling people,
nor weakening them, or
even knocking them out.
It doesn't inflict one external action.
All it does is make them mad.
It awakens combative instinct in the
limbic system of people's brains.
Just a little at first,
and then it proliferates.
Because one woman said he smelled bad,
he drove the entire group
into a bloody brawl.
One that ended in carnage.
Earlier, you said it was
beyond anyone's control, right?
Yes, it's an unusable stand.
It can't distinguish
between enemies and allies.
If there's infighting among your
subordinates, your organization falls apart.
So then, may I have that?
If you don't need it, just the stand.
Are you going to remove the
power and keep it as a disc?
Because if so, that just might work out.
The exact right person, at the
exact right place and moment,
that time might be nigh.
Well, these mushrooms
might be okay to eat.
Guess I'll try some.
Not bad, actually.
FE40536, it's time for your shower.
Up and at them!
My eyes! Ha! I told you! She
did it! Look at that! She hid!
She scurried under that
bed like a cockroach.
Looks like I win for this cell.
That'll be $20, a deal's a deal.
Pay up, pal. Damn.
Come on, man.
All I got on me right now is $15.
How about a discount?
Yeah, sorry, Kent.
Yeah, no shit.
Anyway, now I just have to feel around
with my thread and hope I find the bone.
No, I have to find it.
What kind of bone is it anyway?
Ironic, I don't even know yet.
Either way, I know it's somewhere
in this discipline cell building.
Someone in here has it.
If I get my hands on it first, that
creepy palesnake will soon follow.
Also, there's my father's stolen memory
disk that the bastard is still holding onto.
Whoa, hey, park it!
Who told you to stand up?
By the way, what's the over-undersome
drama at the Marlins game tonight?
I'm not holding my breath.
The starting pitcher and the on-field
broadcaster lady just broke up.
He'll be off his game tonight for sure.
I'll bet you the $15 from early.
You got a deal.
Seriously, do you even have the cash?
He's going to get yanked
in the first inning.
No way.
Three up, three down.
Mark it.
Okay, sucker.
It's your money.
Aren't you excited for tonight?
Sorry about that.
This valve gets a little sticky sometimes.
Oh, thanks a lot.
I've got nothing else to change into
unless I go back to the main building.
Hey, what the hell was that for?
I told you I was sorry.
It's not like I splashed
you on purpose man.
Wait, what? You're
crazy. I didn't touch you
What is going on with you?
There's no way I could
have hit you that hard
Back the fuck off Westwood.
You don't like that.
We'll pay back to bits liquor
Asshole!
Bastard!
Get off me!
Okay, fine, I give!
I give, I said!
Stop, stop, stop!
Knock it off, please! I'm sorry!
If you don't have a change of
clothes, I'll lend you some!
Is that gonna be okay with you?
Come on, let's stop this shit already!
Westwood, I've never seen you this way.
You've gotta calm down!
What, did someone put
hot sauce in your shorts?
What do you say, little buddy?
We're still friends.
Am I right?
Gotta hand it to you, old pal.
You pack a good punch.
I'm ready, bring it on!
What the actual hell is
wrong with these assholes?
Hold on, could it be?
Oh, I'm getting excited.
What definition?
What sparkling vigor?
I can see every point of
power in that ripped lake.
Every single muscle is
a gorgeous work of art.
It's beautiful!
And I can tap right into
where all his strengths are.
I see the raw beauty of
battle, and I love it!
Okay, this just got even weirder.
And what's with their backs?
Those things that look like
flashlights or something.
Let's go!
Just FYI, you have no chance!
I'm gonna reduce you to
a stain on the floor!
Yeah, I am a golden god!
Wait, is this actually a stand attack?
Is that guard the enemy?
No, the enemy hasn't revealed itself yet.
But this is a stand.
I know it is.
This abnormality is a stand attack.
Do not give what is holy to the dogs,
lest they trample them under their feet,
and turn and tear you in pieces.
Matthew 7-6
Regrettably, Sports Maximum is missing.
I don't know how or why
they were able to find out,
but there is no doubt they've
read through Maximum's memories?
and this is a rather large problem.
To fix this, I've sent four STAN users
to the Disciplined Cell building.
However...
If Jolene Kujo has found
her way to the Disciplined
Cell in pursuit of Dio's priceless bone...
I cannot allow her to live anymore.
There is no choice.
And I will make sure it's done right.
I don't care how it happens as long as
it's in the Disciplined Cell building.
Those four people will do
anything and everything
to ensure the total eradication
of Jotaro's daughter.
Everything is riding on it.
Hang on, is he letting them out?
I can see your point
of power in all of you.
I can see where your
strengths lie from here.
Your most dominant muscle groups.
And they're glorious.
Welcome to Fight Club!
Bring it on, bitches!
Although
you
think I cope.
My head is filled with hope.
Of some place
other than here.
Although you think I smile.
Inside and all the while.
I'm wondering about my destiny?
I'm thinking
about all the
things I'd like
to do in my life.
I'm a dreamer.
A distant dreamer.
Dreaming far away.
From today!
Thank you.